# **HAMZA DELLAM**

## Software Developer

+212 658-844-363 • hamzadellam@hotmail.com • hamzadlm.github.io/hdlm\_portfolio/ 240 Gamma C8, El Jadida, Morocco.

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Software developer at DIGIEYE with an overall experience of 5 years. Open to the realm of technology and innovation, especially in the fields of software development, automation and digital transformation. Mostly a backend developer but have experience with all phases of the software development life-cycle, from system design to deployment. Can be efficiently autonomous, work within a team, or, if required, work fully independently. Ready for new challenges.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Software Developer Aug 2021 - Present

DIGIEYE • Casablanca

Build and maintain web applications and microservices.

Participate in the entire application lifecycle from planning, researching to testing and deploying.

Develop and maintain multiple dashboards and reports.

Mining data from different sources using scrapping tools like Selenium, Requests and others.

Creating and hosting Bots and automated solutions for different scenarios.

Aeronautics Engineer Nov 2020 – Aug 2021

Tech Mahindra • Casablanca

Execute methods workload for project Global 6500 / 5500.

Lead a team of agents, ensure workload distribution and schedule the workplan.

Track KPI, ensure high efficiency and plan activities and actions to increase CSAT score

Identify automation capable tasks and develop solutions for multiple types of processes using Python.

Generate revenue through time-reduction solutions.

Provide training and document processes and create How-To guides.

Team Leader Jul 2018 - Nov 2020

**BOMBARDIER** • Casablanca

Lead a methods team & maintain high levels of KPI & Verify the conformity of products.

Establish communication between client and supplier & automate repetitive processes and maintain high efficiency.

Mission Workshop Jul 2018 - Nov 2020

BOMBARDIER • Belgium / Germany

Assist different workshops.

Plan meetings with Automation CoE manager and provide feedback of opportunities.

Provide feedback from production environments.

Methods Agent Sep 2017 - Jul 2018

BOMBARDIER • Casablanca

Produce, verify and correct work packages for different projects.

EDUCATION

Oct 2018 - Sep 2019

Master's degree - Industrial Engineering and Management

Verified International Academic Qualification - World Education Services. ID 4779226IMM

### **SKILLS**

- Backend: Python Django FastAPI Flask MySQL PostgreSQL Redis MongoDB.
- Frontend: Javascript VueJS HTML CSS.
- Data Science: Python PowerBI Pandas NumPy Excel.
- Automation: Scripting Power Automate Selenium RPA.
- DevOps: Git GitHub Docker OpenShift.
- OS: Windows Linux macOS.
- Languages: English IELTS C1 French TEF C1 Arabic Native Korean Basics (currently learning).